They only look like the perfect couple.
Anyone But You is a romance, comedy film directed by Will Gluck.
After an amazing first date, Bea and Ben’s fiery attraction turns ice cold — until they
find themselves unexpectedly reunited at a destination wedding in Australia.
So they do what any two mature adults would do: pretend to be a couple.
Bea, played by Sydney Sweeney.
Ben, played by Glen Powell.
Barista, played by Mia Artemis.
Miranda Clerk, played by Nat Buchanan.
Pete, played by GaTa.
Claudia, played by Alexandra Shipp.
Anyone but You is a 2023 American romantic comedy film
starring Sydney Sweeney and Glen Powell.
Based on Much Ado About Nothing by William Shakespeare, the film was
directed by Will Gluck, and written by Ilana Wolpert and Gluck.
The supporting cast includes Alexandra Shipp, GaTa, Hadley Robinson, Michelle Hurd,
Dermot Mulroney, Darren Barnet, Bryan Brown, and Rachel Griffiths.
Anyone but You premiered at the AMC Lincoln Square Theater on December 11, 2023, and was released
theatrically in the United States by Sony Pictures Releasing on December 22, 2023.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and emerged as a
sleeper hit, grossing over $220 million worldwide.
This success was seen as the return of romantic comedies to theaters.
The film explores themes of australia, hiking, romcom,
based on play or musical, law school.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.